let questions=[
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "JavaScript is the ____ type language.",
        answer:"Object-Oriented",
        options:[
        "Object-Oriented",
        "Object Based",
        "Procedural",
        "None of the above"
        ]
        
    },
    {
        numb:2,
        question: "What keyword is used to check whether a given property is valid or not?",
        answer:"in",
        options:[
        "in",
        "is in",
        "exists",
        "lies"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:3,
        question: "What is the use of the <nonscript> tag in JavaScript?",
        answer:"The contents are displayed by non-JS-based browsers.",
        options:[
        "The contents are displayed by non-JS-based browsers.",
        "Clears all the cookies and cache.",
        "Both A and B.",
        "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:4,
        question:"Q4: When an operator's value is NULL, the type of returned by the unary operator is.",
        answer:"Object",
        options:[
        "Boolean",
        "Undefined",
        "Object",
        "Integer"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:5,
        question:"Q5: What does the JavaScript 'debugger' statements do?",
        answer:"It acts as a breakpoint in a program",
        options:[
        "It will debug all the errors in the program at runtime.",
        "It acts as a breakpoint in a program",
        "It will debug error in the current statement if any",
        "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:6,
        question:"What does the 'toLocateString()' method do in JS?",
        answer:"Returns a localised string representation of an object.",
        options:[
        "Returns a localised object representation.",
        "Returns a parsed string.",
        "Returns a localised string representation of an object.",
        "None of the above."
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:7,
        question:"The process in which an object or data structure is translated into a format suitable for transferral over a network, or storage is called?",
        answer:"Object Serialization",
        options:[
        "Object Serialization",
        "Object Encapsulation",
        "Object Inheritance",
        "None of the above",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:8,
        question:"Which function is used to serialize an object into a JSON string in Javascript?",
        answer:"stringify()",
        options:[
        "stringify()",
        "parse()",
        "convert()",
        "None of the above",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:9,
        question:"The 3 basic object attributes in Javascript are:",
        answer:"class, prototype, Object's extensible flag.",
        options:[
        "Class, prototype, objects' parameters.",
        "class, prototype, Object's extensible flag.",
        "class, parameters, object's extensible flag.",
        "Classes, Native object, and Interfaces and Object's extensible flag.",
        ]
    },
    {

        question:"Q10: Which of the following is not a Javascript framework?",
        a:"Node",
        b:"Vue",
        c:"React",
        d:"Cassandra",
        ans:"ans4"
    }

];